<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipe Project</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="mainTitle">Recipes</string>
    <string name="mainTagLine">~Mitchel Millsaps~</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">LOVE MUSIC</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 albums</string>

    <string-array name="breakfast_name">
        <item>"Banana Bread"</item>
        <item>"Chef Baked Eggs"</item>
        <item>"Fluffy Pancakes"</item>
        <item>"Sausage Balls"</item>
        <item>"Sausage Egg Casserole"</item>
        <item>"Tomatoes &amp; Bacon Egg"</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="breakfast_author_name">
        <item>"By Awais"</item>
        <item>"By Danish"</item>
        <item>"By Ali"</item>
        <item>"By Safdar"</item>
        <item>"By Amjad"</item>
        <item>"By Danish"</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="breakfast_time">
        <item>"30 mins"</item>
        <item>"6 h"</item>
        <item>"19 h"</item>
        <item>"23 h"</item>
        <item>"2 days"</item>
        <item>"1 week"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="breakfast_fav">
        <item>"5"</item>
        <item>"0"</item>
        <item>"50"</item>
        <item>"30"</item>
        <item>"16"</item>
        <item>"9"</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ingredition">
        <item>"5"</item>
        <item>"0"</item>
        <item>"50"</item>
        <item>"30"</item>
        <item>"16"</item>
        <item>"9"</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="breakfast_description">

        <item>"Set out all your ingredients.
Set a stove element with a pan to medium heat.
Combine the 4 dry ingredients (flour, sugar, baking powder -- two Tablespoons, not two Teaspoons as some have suggested, salt) in a bowl.
Add the soy milk and vegetable oil to your mixture.
Mix until smooth.
Now the pan should be ready for your batter, so spoon one pancakes' worth of the mixture into the pan.
Flip [carefully] when you see bubbles in the middle of the pancake, or if the edges are looking stiffened.
Repeat until the batter is gone, and try not to eat them all while you're cooking them."
        </item>

        <item>"Cut up apple (with or without skin - your choice) into bite sized chunks.
Put the chopped apple into a container with a lid (ex. an empty margarine container).
Sprinkle on the cinnamon, put the lid on the container, and gently shake so cinnamon covers apple.
Eat and enjoy immediately."
        </item>

        <item>"Preheat oven to 350 degrees.
Grease and flour two 9 x 5-inch loaf pans.
Combine flour, cinnamon, baking soda and salt in large bowl.
Combine sugar, pumpkin, eggs, vegetable oil and apple juice in large mixer bowl; beat until just blended.
Add pumpkin mixture to flour mixture; stir just until moistened.
Fold in apples.
Spoon batter into prepared loaf pans.
Bake for 65 to 70 minutes or until wooden pick inserted in center comes out clean.
Cool in pans on wire racks for 10 minutes; remove to wire racks to cool completely.
To make using three 8 X 4-inch loaf pans: Prepare as above and bake for 60 to 65 minutes.
To make using five or six 5 X 3-inch mini-loaf pans: Prepare as above and bake for 55 to 60 minutes."
        </item>

        <item>"Mix all the ingredients together until thoroughly blended (it is best to use your hands or an electric mixer).
Form into about 4 dozen 1 to 1 1/2 inch balls and place on a cookie sheet or broiler pan.
Bake at 375°F for about 25 minutes.
Once they are cool, they can be sorted into individual zip bags and frozen for a grab-and-go breakfast.
NOTE: for Scotch Eggs, mold a bit of the raw meat mixture around a peeled hard-boiled egg (or eggs) and bake at 350°F for 30 minutes."</item>

        <item>"Preheat oven according to directions on crescent roll package.
Unroll but leave intact 2 triangles of crescent rolls.
Pinch seam together and cut lengthwise into 5 strips and then cross-wise to make 10 strips.
Roll each strip around one sausage and place in baking pan that has been sprayed with non-stick cooking oil.
Sprinkle each pig with parmesan and garlic salt.
Bake according to crescent roll package directions."</item>

        <item>"Beat egg until fluffy.
Add milk and melted margarine.
Add dry ingredients and mix well.
Heat a heavy griddle or fry pan which is greased with a little butter on a paper towel.
The pan is hot enough when a drop of water breaks into several smaller balls which 'dance' around the pan.
Pour a small amount of batter (approx 1/4 cup) into pan and tip to spread out or spread with spoon.
When bubbles appear on surface and begin to break, turn over and cook the other side."
        </item>

        <item>"Mix the dry items first.
Combine the eggs and melted butter to the milk and slowly stir into the flour mixture.
Let sit at least 10 minutes while heating the pan.
These will be high, but light and fluffy -- ."</item>

        <item>"In a large mixing bowl, whisk together all dry ingredients.
Separate the eggs, adding the yolks to the dry ingredient mixture, and placing the whites in a small mixing bowl.
Beat whites until moderately stiff; set aside.
Add milk and melted butter to dry ingredient mixture and blend.
Fold stiff egg whites into mixture.
Ladle mixture into hot waffle iron and bake."</item>

        <item>"Sift the dry ingredients together in a large bowl.
Separate the eggs.
In small bowl, beat egg whites until stiff.
Mix together the egg yolks, milk and oil and stir slightly.
Add to dry ingredients and mix well.
Fold in beaten egg whites.
Cook in waffle iron."</item>

        <item>"Combine all ingredients (use less pepper if you don't want a spicy taste) and blend well.
If time permits, refrigerate overnight to let the meat absorb the flavor of the spices.
Form into patties and cook as needed, freezing leftovers.
Don't overcook or they will dry out--remove from the heat as soon as they're no longer pink inside, but still juicy. (if you prefer a moister texture, you add a splash of olive oil or an egg to the mixture just prior to cooking)."
        </item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
